<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="description19">This bird is known for its black shiny plumage, gregarious nature, and stretching its wings out to dry. Breeding plumage includes white at the base of the bill. The underside is lighter. Juveniles are brown. Native to wetlands and other aquatic ecosystems, it consumes fish, crustaceans, frogs, and aquatic insects.</string>
    <string name="description23">The bird is white with a yellow beak, and blackish feet. During the breeding period, it has long aigrette feathers in its dorsal and chest. It travels in flocks often, and lives in the wetlands close by. It eats fish, snakes, and crustaceans. During the nineteenth century it was hunted for its elegant feathers.</string>
    <string name="description29">One of this bird\’s names comes from its sing, which sounds like a flute. It is very colorful bird, with a bluish-black head and back-neck feathers, a light blue-grey back, a yellowish chest and neck. It is covered in cinnamon grooves and has a pink beak with a black tip. Adolescents are more pale. It eats insects, more than other herons. It lives in savannas, pastures, and flooded fields.</string>
    <string name="description32">The Black-crowned night-heron is gregarious, arboreal, crepuscular, and appears hunched. It has a robust beak and plumage that is usually grey with a black crown, whitish ventral, and yellowish legs. The young are brown with spots and white streaks. They live in flooded marshes and savannas and eat a variety of foods including fish, insects, and garbage. As a defense mechanism, chicks vomit when people approach the nest.</string>
    <string name="description35">This bird can be identified by its red feet and eyes, its straight beak and its white feathers with wings that are partially black.  Juveniles have black plumage until they are three months old.  The bird eats fish, frogs, insects, and more. The stork moves around depending on weather and food conditions, but it does not migrate.</string>
    <string name="description37">This distinctive bird has a curved beak, a shining olive-colored body with a white front, tousled neck feathers, and white grooves. It has reddish eyes and legs. The adolescents are more dull in color. They live in estuaries and floodplains. They eat insects and molluscs.</string>
    <string name="description40">This bird is seen in small or medium sized groups, sometimes with other species. It is bright green. The bird flies with its rose-colored legs above its tail. It has a pinkish face, with a curved ivory beak (during mating season, it is also pinkish). This bird lives in estuaries, floodplains, and lagoons. It eats insects and other invertebrates.</string>
    <string name="description57">This trusting bird is the most common bird found in the wetlands. The bird is mostly brown with black on its head, neck, spine, wings, and tail. Its face and neck are clear and appear bluish. The bird also has a white triangular patch on its internal flight feathers. Its beak and feet are red. Females have white spots, a white throat, and a grey beak. Females fly in front of the males.</string>
    <string name="description67">This bird, found in many diverse environments, is very trusting and gregarious. They can be seen flying in groups or roosting in trees. When flying, the bird flaps its wings often, with force. It has a short black tail and a black head.  When it is flying, with its wings horizontal, a noticeable patch of white can be seen in its feathers.  The Black Vulture eats roadkill.</string>
    <string name="description82">This bird flaps its wings a lot in flight. It is of medium height and the top of its head is dark brown. The back of its wingtips are reddish, and are prominent in flight. Its front is grooved and barred, and it has a barred blackish tail. On adolescents, there is a brown front, wide brow, and throat. Its back is ochre. This bird lives at the edges of forests, savannas, and groves, sometimes near roads. It eats insects and other small prey.</string>
    <string name="description98">The Great Black-hawk has black plumage and white feathers on the tip of its short tail.  Its beak is yellow and black.  The bird is sluggish and flies very slowly.  For food, it often eats insects, reptiles, and carrion.</string>
    <string name="description100">The Snail Kite is a gregarious bird that lives in the wetlands. It flies slowly in order to see the water or to glide at high altitudes. It is able to see the water from both high and low altitudes. It has a thin, hooked beak and orange legs. The males appear blackish, with a white posterior. The females and young birds have brown plumage. They have spotted ventrals and symmetrical faces. All Snail kites eat aquatic snails, in particular those of the Pomacea genus.</string>
    <string name="description146">This bird flies low to the ground and is brownish black in color.  It has a long neck, with white stripes, and a yellow beak.  The bird\'s legs are long just like its beak.  Its beak evolved especially to eat apple snails.  According to Guaraní legend, the stark, evoking call of the Limpkin is the mourning of a teenager for his mother.</string>
    <string name="description153">This bird\'s outer feathers are bright green and brown. It has a brownish back and a black chest. Its front is also black, and it has a fine tuft on its neck. Its rich black flight feathers and belt are notable in flight. The rest of the bird is white. It has redish eyelids and eyes, a red beak, and red feet. The bird eats terrestrial invertebrates. It is an aggressive bird, especially when defending its nest. It can be found in meadows, rural areas, and wetlands.</string>
    <string name="description156">This bird has long feet and toes and yellow flight feathers. Its long toes and claws allow it to walk on the surface of lagoons. Females are generally larger than males. This bird feeds on insects and other invertebrates found in the wetlands. </string>
    <string name="description174">This bird lives in estuaries and sometimes can be found resting on posts. It has a black tail with a cinnamon colored band, and a grooved chest. Its back is greyish-brown and its front is white. It has a large beak, of up to 7 cm, and olive-yellow legs. Adolescents have shorter beaks and bluish legs.</string>
    <string name="description224">The Smooth-billed Ani is a confident bird that is in boisterous groups. It has a curved, long, and thin beak and black plumage with bright violet. Its blue tail is long, broad, and oscillates. There are iridescent arrows on its neck and chest. It lives in savannas and rural areas and eats small vertebrates and fruit.</string>
    <string name="description240">This terrestrial, diurnal bird lives in meadows, savannas, and rural areas. It is found resting on posts, in its cave, or near other burrowing owls. It’s a whitish bird that has large legs and no ears. Its back is brown, with white freckles, and its front is generally spotted. It has a barred tail and a a white brow and throat. It eats small vertebrates and large arthropods.</string>
    <string name="description277">The males have bright green feathers, with a blue tail, greenish blue throat and breast, and a red beak with a black apex. The females have a modest coloration, with and a colonic line and a whitish apex, and grey ventral. This hummingbird lives in forests, savannas, and villages.</string>
    <string name="description278">Most of the Gilded Sapphire Hummingbird’s body is covered with green plumage with a golden sheen. It has a tan tail and cinnamon-colored neck. The females are similar, with a dull green and greyish abdomen. This bird is found in savannas, villages, and forests.</string>
    <string name="description294">This bird is found in the wetlands. Its head and back are bright green, and males’ chests are reddish-blond while females’ are green and white. It has a superior coat without white specks and stretchmarked sides. The rest of its ventral is white. It has a large beak.</string>
    <string name="description309">This terrestrial bird is found in savannas, closed fields, pastures, and rural areas. On the contrary to other carpenter birds, this bird is terrestrial, eating ants and termites. The bird can be identified by its black and white striped back.</string>
    <string name="description343">This bird has a brownish grey or brown back. Its wingtips have a slightly noticeable cinnamon color. It has a reddish brown tail and a whitish throat. The rest of its front is greyish brown or slightly cinnamon colored. The bird makes nests out of mud, like little ovens, that can be seen in many different places. It is terrestrial and walks with elegance. The birds sing in pairs, each with different notes. It can be found in a wide variety of environments and populations.</string>
    <string name="description348">This well colored bird is found in brush, savannas, and rural areas. It has a very long forked tail. It also has a reddish head and shoulders, a cinnamon colored chest, and yellow beneath its beak. Its back has black grooves and its throat is black flanked with white. Adolescent birds have shorter tails. These birds make large nests and make a deep clucking noise.</string>
    <string name="description369">This bird is dark brown, with a reddish head, wings, and tail. It has yellow eyes.  The bird is commonly found in open forests and trees nearby water.</string>
    <string name="description387">This bird is found in thickets, rural areas, and gardens. When it sings, it balances its head and closes its tail. In addition, it gives a rhythmic series of clucks, sometimes in pairs, that accelerates and lowers, concluding with a distinguished note. The bird is black barred with white and has small black tufts, ivory eyes, and light-blue legs. The females are distinct for their small reddish tufts, reddish back, cinnamon colored chest, and a face and neck that is grey with black stripes.</string>
    <string name="description446">The Spectacled Tyrant is black with white primary feathers noticeable in flight. Its beak and periocular are yellowish. In general, the spectacled tyrant is aloof and inconspicuous. Its wings produce a ruffling sound when it flies. It eats insects that it catches in the mud.</string>
    <string name="description447">This bird has a black back, wings, eyes, and legs. The other parts of the bird are shiny and white. They mainly eat insects that they find in the ground. They sit at the tops of trees, in bushes, and on posts.</string>
    <string name="description454">The Great Kiskadee is a common, well-known, and daring bird that lives in diverse environments. It has a large head with a yellowish semi-crown. Also, there are long, cinnamon-colored lines on its flight feathers and whitish-yellow ventral feathers. It eats insects, fish, small reptiles, and other animals.</string>
    <string name="description458">The Tropical Kingbird lives in forests, savannas, and other environments. It is often seen in high, visible places. It has a threaded triangular tail with a hidden orange crown and grey cap. Its dorsum plumage and chest are olivaceous grey. The rest of its ventral plumage is yellowish gold. It eats flying insects and fruit.</string>
    <string name="description488">This bird lives in savannas, on the edge of the Chaco\'s forests, and in rural areas. It is a white bird with black eyes and feet and a pointed beak. Its primary feathers and the point of its tail are black. According to legend, this melancholic bird lost its lover and, as a sign of its grief, is white with a black band around its wings.</string>
    <string name="description534">This bird lives in savannas and rural areas, frequently near water and in oven-like nests. They have brown backs and collars, a white chest, and a slightly forked tail. It glides with its wings below the horizontal. It eats insects in flight.</string>
    <string name="description549">The Chalk-browed Mockingbird has a pleasant call and can intimidate other species. Its back is black and brown, and its tail is long and semi-erect. It is found in savannas, borders of forests, rural areas, and villages.</string>
    <string name="description617">This bird is found in forests, savannas, and rural or populated areas. It is a confident bird, and it can be seen in pairs or groups, sometimes on trails, but more often in the bushes. The bird has many calls, and some are chirps. Its front is white and its beak is off-white. Its chest and head are red. Juveniles have a more pale head. This bird is omnivorous.</string>
    <string name="description631">This unmistakable bird is black and cinnamon colored. It has a black collar and face. Its throat and parts of its head are white. The females have white throats. The rest of its front is cinnamon colored. This bird is found in estuaries, flooded pastures, and aquatic vegetation.</string>
    <string name="description639">This bird has a greyish back. Its front and notable wingtips are white, and its beak is dark orange. The females have a common design and cinnamon colored front. It is found in pastures and thickets near the water.</string>
    <string name="description647">These birds are trusting and usually are seen in pairs on the sides of roads. From the tops of bushes, their song is pleasant, penetrating and short. The bird has a grey head and olive colored back with blackish stripes. Its wings and tail are greenish. Its orange beak, with a black culman, is prominent. The adolescents are very grooved and have blackish beaks. Their brow is yellow and their backbone and abdomen are cinnamon colored. This bird is found in savannas, wet pastures, and reed beds.</string>
    <string name="description667">This bird forms large groups with other species. They sit on cattle, and you can see them in many places, including populated places. They eat a wide variety, including seeds and insects. Like with other cowbirds, it is a parasite on other birds. The males are black with bright violet. The females are blackish grey and tinged brown.</string>
    <string name="description669">This bird has a long and sharp beak and a black tail. Its front is yellow while its sides have black stripes. Males\' entire bodies are black, while females are yellow and brown. The bird eats insects, small vertebrates, and seeds.</string>
    <string name="description677">This bird has a strong and clear call. Its beak is long and black. The bird\'s head is orange and red. Generally, they fly in pairs. The bird feeds off of insects and sometimes small frogs. </string>
</resources>